Brittany Bobb

Fort Collins, Colorado (757) 707-4380

Brittany.Bobb@colostate.edu linedin.com/in/brittanv-bobb-

As a technician with the Crow Valley Livestock Cooperative Inc., I apply my skills and knowledge in biodiversity, ecosystem services, botany, ecosystem ecology, and data management to contribute to our projects and team at the USDA. I work with a team of passionate and dedicated professionals who share the mission of tackling pressing climate challenges. I am currently pursuing a bachelor's degree in Ecosystem Science and Sustainability with a minor in Ecological Restoration at Colorado State University, where I learn from leading experts in the field and participate in hands-on projects and research. I earned an Associate of Science degree from Front Range Community College and gained a solid foundation in biology, chemistry, and environmental science. My goal is to contribute to the conservation and restoration of natural habitats and ecosystems, with a vision to inspire community engagement in environmental stewardship.

Education:

Bachelor of Ecological Science and Sustainability 08/2023- Current **GPA 3.1** Minor: Ecological Restoration Colorado State University, Fort Collins, Colorado

Relevant Work Experience:

Technician, Crow Valley Livestock Cooperative Inc. 10/2024- Current Fort Collins, Colorado Biological Science Aid, USDA 05/2024-10/2024 Fort Collins, Colorado 03/2022-05/2024 Greenhouse Employee, Fort Collins Nursery Fort Collins, Colorado

Additional Experience:

Volunteer and Member, Volunteers for Outdoor Colorado

04/2023- Current

Denver, Colorado

- Forest Health @ Berrian Mountain Park
 - Assisted a Sawyer with the removal of unhealthy lodgepole pine trees according to the prescription. The fuel management work aided the local fire mitigation plan.
- Habitat Restoration @ Moon Pass

Assisted in removing the invasive Oxeye Daisy, improving the health of the native plant population. Because the volunteer effort of this multiyear project has been so successful, the land manager has opted to no longer treat this area with chemical herbicides.

Trail Maintenance @ Ridgeway State Park

Participated in the construction of a retaining rock wall, contributed to the widening and grading of the existing trail, and helped with the construction of minor drainage ditches. This project aimed to improve the longevity of the trail, while enhancing accessibility, and fostering safety.

Accomplishments:

Phi Theta Kappa Member

02/2022- Current 04/2024- Current

Xi Sigma Pi Member Omicron Chapter